everythingetsy.com 2016-05-07

# Privacy Policy

## Your privacy is critically important to us. At Crazy Tree Media, Inc. we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy.

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our [support team](http://www.everythingetsy.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us").

Crazy Tree Media, Inc. Inc. (“ **Crazy Tree Media, Inc.** ”) operates several websites including [EverythingEtsy.com](http://everythingetsy.com/), [Etsypreneur.com](http://etsypreneur.com/), [HandmadeandCraft.com](http://handmadeandcraft.com/), [RemodelingGuy.net](http://remodelingguy.net/), and [RemodelingTherapy.com](http://remodelingtherapy.com/). It is Crazy Tree Media, Inc.’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Crazy Tree Media, Inc. collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Crazy Tree Media, Inc.’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Crazy Tree Media, Inc.’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Crazy Tree Media, Inc. may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Crazy Tree Media, Inc. also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blogs. Crazy Tree Media, Inc. only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Crazy Tree Media, Inc.’s websites choose to interact with Crazy Tree Media, Inc. in ways that require Crazy Tree Media, Inc. to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Crazy Tree Media, Inc. gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a user account to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Crazy Tree Media, Inc. are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Crazy Tree Media, Inc. collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Crazy Tree Media, Inc.. Crazy Tree Media, Inc. does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Crazy Tree Media, Inc. may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Crazy Tree Media, Inc. may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Crazy Tree Media, Inc. does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Crazy Tree Media, Inc. discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Crazy Tree Media, Inc.’s behalf or to provide services available at Crazy Tree Media, Inc.’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Crazy Tree Media, Inc.’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Crazy Tree Media, Inc. will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Crazy Tree Media, Inc. discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Crazy Tree Media, Inc. believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Crazy Tree Media, Inc., third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Crazy Tree Media, Inc. website and have supplied your email address, Crazy Tree Media, Inc. may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Crazy Tree Media, Inc. and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Crazy Tree Media, Inc. takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Crazy Tree Media, Inc. uses cookies to help Crazy Tree Media, Inc. identify and track visitors, their usage of Crazy Tree Media, Inc. website, and their website access preferences. Crazy Tree Media, Inc. visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Crazy Tree Media, Inc.’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Crazy Tree Media, Inc.’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If Crazy Tree Media, Inc., or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Crazy Tree Media, Inc. goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Crazy Tree Media, Inc. may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Crazy Tree Media, Inc. and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
